midsecurity.com 2012-03-13

# Privacy Policy | MidSecurity

In a common situation and condition, MidSecurity will never practice to disclose personal information to third parties. We may share personal information in two instances. Firstly, we may share personal information with our contractors and service providers in order to maintain, enhance, or add to the functionality of the MidSecurity web service. Secondly, we may share personal information with third parties such as the government or other entities when required to by law or as required by court order. MidSecurity respects the privacy and rights of its visitors. No effort is made to identify individuals without their rights, permissions, and knowledge.

MidSecurity are heavily committed to your privacy and security as why we launch this website. We despise spam, adware, and other malicious scripts that can harm our visitors. We believe people who send spam and those kinds of harmful things should spend time in prison for wasting the world\'s time depends on the rules enforce in all countries respectively. Maintaining the privacy, security, and integrity of your account is very crucial and of paramount importance to us. If you would like to see our privacy policy include something else, then please get in contact with us.

### What kind of information do we collect and use for?

We collect information from you when you access on our site. When accessing our site or joining our forum, you may appropriately be asked to enter your private identity. However, you may visit our site anonymously. Therefore, any information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 1. to personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); 2. to improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).

### Do we disclose any information to external parties?

We will strictly not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

At some certain condition, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Terms of Use

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use and the services of our website at [Term of Use](http://www.midsecurity.com/term).

### Considerations

By accessing and using our site, we think that you have understood and considered things regarding to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our statements in our Privacy Policy, we will definitely inform those changes through this page immediately.
